madeit.com.au 2012-10-03

# madeit - the handmade market open all day every day :: buy & sell australian handmade :: online handmade market :: art :: craft :: design

The security of your personal information is important to us and we are committed to maintaining the privacy of our customers and securing any details you provide us. We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. However no method of transmission over the internet or method of electronic storage is 100% secure.

The amount of information we collect about you depends on how you use our website and how much information you elect to provide.

When you visit our website, we automatically record information such as your server address, domain name, the date and time of your visit and the information downloaded. We use this information to assist us in better understanding the interests and preferences of our customers, aimed at providing you with a more tailored service.

If you provide personal information, those details are stored securely and may be used to send you marketing material and for statistical purposes. However, madeit cannot warrant the security of any information sent over the internet to us and we are not responsible for circumstances where that information is accessed without authorisation.

|  | 

**** We have no ability to view your credit card details as this information is encrypted as soon as you submit it.

Personal information will not be intentionally disclosed outside of our organisation (or related entities) without your consent, except where we are required or permitted to do so at law.

We will only permit your personal information to be accessed by authorised madeit personnel and we will take reasonable steps to ensure your personal information is accurate and up to date and protected from risks such as unauthorised access, modification or disclosure.

To protect your personal information, madeit uses international grade SSL encryption where appropriate to protect any information you have requested and any information you send against access by a third party. If your browser does not support SSL, or if you are connecting to the Internet from behind a firewall, pages may not display correctly. If that is the case, please note that you may not be able to use this website.

If at anytime you would like to remove your personal details from our database, or you have any queries regarding our Terms of Use or Privacy Policy, please contact us using the “Contact Us” link.
